[{"answer": "Well, if I was to understand, I'd say you've asked me a compound question.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "In your experience with this kind of thing, would that entirely surprise you, or is there often a copycat element to these kinds of massacres?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "EGG: I'm with the group United Physicians in Newtown.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "How does America move to a safer place, do you think?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Has anything quite prepared you for the horrors that you saw that day in December?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "A couple of things.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "As one of the people who had to quite literally pick up the pieces of some of those children, what do you say by response?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "I have profiled so many fugitives on \"America's Most Wanted\" that were on parole or probation, a guy that we caught several years ago, Joseph Duncan, who is a suspect in four murders of children, an entire family to get at a kid, to kidnap their 8-year-old daughter and 9-year-old son, released and was able to get a gun every time.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What do we do about this and what do we do about the connection between clear mental health issue and the type of gun violence we saw at Aurora or Sandy Hook or these other massacres?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I think every person, and I -- most people I know don't know their two U.S. senators, other members of the Congress, they have to say, I will never vote for you again.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Final question, very quickly, who will stand up to the NRA?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "We're always determined to have the baby.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Did you and your girlfriend ever consider having an abortion, or were you always determined to have the baby?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "Well, it didn't surprise me from her father, but her mother, yes, it surprised me.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "So when you heard that her parents were adamant that you would not have the child and that they wanted their daughter to have a termination, how did it make you feel?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "No, I mean, I tried just to keep my mouth shut.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Did you have arguments with them?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Well, the precedent has been around for a while.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "What is the precedent that's being set here, do you think?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, you know, as Stephen said the -- you know, we like to say the \"Roe v. Wade\" decision goes both ways.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "How important is the \"Roe v. Wade\" ruling in this case?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Yes, I definitely have the determination to be a good father.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Do you have the determination to be a good father?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Do you plan to get married?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "And do you think that you can repair the relationship with your in-laws, as they will be, or your girlfriend's parents?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yes, I can see that.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Do you believe that they will in the end come around to being loving grandparents?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Piers, I definitely understand how the parents feel, because I think they probably understand that when a teenager is pregnant -- she's 16 years old -- and her boyfriend, the father of the child to be, is 16 years old, it's going to be the most important economic turning point in that girl's life, if she takes the pregnancy to term and gives birth.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "What do you make of this case?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "I was saying in the Green Room, it would be really nice if the family members of first families that are living really get together, have their own party at the White House for a charitable cause that they like, instead of always listening to the fathers and whomever get together and do something good for the world.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "You get together like a little club, isn't it?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "No, it's a special day for all Americans, piers.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Is it a special day for you?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "AFT: I do not.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Should it be an impediment to him being president?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "OOVER: Well, the governing principle with all presidents and the media is transparency and keeping open lines of communication.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "And should the American media, on behalf of the public, cut the president a bit of slack?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "You know, when he put together the tax break of 1981, he called Tip O'Neal in the White House and had dinner.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "And what would he have done about it?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Well, all descendents can get in the trap of saying -- pretending like they know exactly what their -- whatever their presidential relative would have said.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "What would he have made of the modern day Republican party?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Well, my great grandfather struggled in his relations with Congress, because he really was a reluctant president.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Do you think that the bipartisan style of previous presidents is just, for whatever reason, not happening?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "I -- I think it's the same as the leader of any organization.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "I'll start with you, John, if I may, what do you think is the primary purpose of a president of the United States?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "I would agree with that.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "I think I agree with Mr. Taft and I agree with Mr. Reagan.", "docId": "130218pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Margaret, what would you say is the point of being a president?", "qSentId": 503}]